When I wake up, I let out a sigh. Somewhere along the way, that became a habit of mine.
I was so sure that love was supposed to be more fun than this.
Wow, you're exactly on time.
I didn't realize that you got here early. Sorry.
It's fine.
I'm sure that the next thing that happens will be me getting rejected.
You see, I... I've had a crush on you ever since we were in our first year. Did you know that?
No.
Didn't think so. I hid it so you wouldn't catch on.
Please don't let him find out how I feel. That was all I could think about.
I'm sure that today will be the last time.
But it hit me when I woke up this morning. That from now on, I no longer have to keep on pretending that I don't like you anymore.
And that gave me a bit of relief.
So it's alright. I have no regrets.
Would you mind hearing me out?
Sure.
You see, I really like the way you play Yamada.
Huh?
I'm talking about gaming. You're so cool-headed, and you don't blame other people.
Uh, huh.
When it comes to PvP games, a lot of other players just lose it, but you never show any signs of that.
Huh.
And I really admired how mature you are in that way.
Thanks.
I also like how you always look out the window when you're spacing out in the classroom.
Hmm?
And I could never tell you because I didn't want you to think I was a fangirl.
But the truth is, I always thought you were super good-looking. And I love the way you never show off.
Oh, and I also love your voice. It really calms me down. And I like your quietness.
I like seeing you walk, and also seeing you run. And I like how you're a slow talker.
You know your habit of blinking a lot when you're at a loss? That.
I've always liked that, too. And I really like how you're equally kind to everyone.
Over the last three years, I'm sure that a lot of girls have fallen for you.
But any way you look at it, I'm sure that I've always liked you more than anyone else.
No question.
I'm sure I've always liked you.
More than anyone else in the world.
I can't really see him.
But...
I managed to tell him everything.
For so long, it felt like a lead weight.
It's been stressing me out all this time.
And that's why...
I absolutely have no regrets.
This was such a relief.
Tsubaki...
I...
I'm really sorry.
I can't return your feelings.
I'm...
What's that?
On your hand.
Huh?
Oh.
This is...
Someone I know did it as a joke.
I know.
The girl who drew that.
She's the girl that...
You're in love with.
Right?
Yes.
Thank you...
For having feelings for me.
I'm really sorry.
I can't feel the same way about you.
It's all right.
Thank you for hearing me out.
I'm glad I told you.
I've known all along.
Because I've been watching you.
I could tell that you'd changed.
Just a little bit.
Even if nobody else noticed.
I could tell right away.
It was nice to get all that off my chest.
Thanks for making time for me.
I'll go...
Home now.
Okay then.
I'll see you at school.
Uh...
I'll, um...
Walk you home?
You don't have your glasses.
And it's dark.
It's fine.
I can go home by myself.
But...
Don't you worry.
I'm not as weak as I look.
Right.
Thank you.
You were so nice to me right to the end.
That made me happy.
That's one of the things I really liked about you.
I really liked you.
We'll be going on break soon.
But I don't know what my work schedule will be like.
What?
It's too noisy?
Oh, sorry.
I'm getting ready to leave the house.
For a meetup with my guilt.
No, Mom.
It's not a club.
I explained it before.
My gaming friends.
Yeah, that's right.
We're all going out tonight to get dinner together.
Hey, I believe that's her now.
See?
Over there.
Hey, you're right.
Akane!
Mr. Kamata, long time no see.
I'm glad you could come.
Thank you.
No, no.
I really appreciate you inviting me.
Kalbi?
I could go for some Kalbi.
I don't know what's Kalbi too!
Hey, Yamata isn't here.
Akita will be arriving later.
Hey-o!
You scared me.
Want me to make you some one-on-one time with him?
He's been pretty busy, so you don't get to see each other much, right?
Darn, I couldn't tell him how I felt the other day.
Nah, that's okay.
I came here today to have some meat with everyone.
Hello and welcome.
That's so.
I have a reservation under Kamata.
We've been waiting for you, Mr. Kamata.
And besides, as for Yamata, he seems to be a little tired lately.
I think studying for his exams is stressing him out.
I'm quite sure that's not the case.
That guy's ready to coast through his entrance exams with flying colors.
No way!
Then I guess I was just imagining things the other day.
This place looks pretty expensive, huh?
I bet the meat costs a ton!
Runa, try to keep your voice down, okay?
But why?
I guess I should tell you a good friend of mine runs this place.
They actually just had their grand opening the other day.
He's been asking me to come check it out,
so I thought it'd be great to share the experience with my guildmates.
Oh, wow, that's amazing!
You sure know a lot of people, Mr. Kamata.
President Kamata!
It's been a while.
Ah, hello there, Inoue.
You look like you're doing well.
Yes, you look well yourself, sir.
So, how's business these days?
We're managing.
Thank you for asking.
Oh, hey, President Kamata.
I didn't know you were here.
Professor Obayashi, what a nice surprise seeing you here.
President Kamata, what a coincidence.
Director Nagaoka, it's good to see you.
Mr. Kamata, what a surprise.
You're President Sumiyoshi's wife, right?
Hello there.
Who would have thought we'd all end up here, huh?
Oh, man, he knows way too many people.
Who even is Mr. Kamata?
Hey!
We've got a whole room all to ourselves!
This meat is so delicious!
And it tastes even better when you're with a lot of people, too, huh?
It really is too bad that our newest guild member couldn't share it with us, though.
I did invite her, but it seems like tonight didn't work for her.
She didn't need to come anyway!
Huh?
Pardon our interruption.
Here you are.
This was sent over by Mr. Inoue from across the hall.
This sake is for Mr. Obayashi.
Mr. Nagaoka sent this over.
And this comes from Mrs. Sumiyoshi.
Oh, my.
They didn't have to do so much for us.
There's even sake!
Crazy!
I've never seen other customers send stuff over.
That's so cool!
Someday I want to become a big shot grown-up, too.
Just like you are!
What are you going on about?
If you ask me, you're already a fine young man.
After all, I'm only able to grind in the dungeons without a care,
because you've graciously taken on all of the guild management duties for me.
Well, that's because I have your support behind the scenes, Mr. Kamota.
Oh, I wouldn't say all that now.
The fact of the matter is, you're always creating fun places to hang out in,
and introducing me to all kinds of great new friends,
so I enjoy each and every day with you.
I hope all of us can keep playing as good friends for as long as time allows.
I hear you!
Bruno wants to keep playing with our guild members forever like always!
Just the current members, though!
Forever like always.
Yeah, but change is necessary as well, you know.
Going forward, our guild will be embracing renewal.
Huh? I'm not here for that!
Why can't we just keep things the way they are?
Change is nothing to be afraid of.
Uh, excuse you, that's the meat Bruna was grilling!
You may think that, but in truth, dear Runa, since I'm the one who raised you,
this Kalbi was actually grilled by meat.
Eita, you suck!
Hello and welcome!
You're one of Mr. Kamata's party, right?
Follow me if you would.
Oh, hey! The attendant's finally here!
Hakun, you're late!
Yo.
Hey, Yamada! Listen to this!
You won't believe the fight Bruna was in just now!
You said you could get here sooner, bud!
Hey, you know...
If you all talk at once...
Uh-oh. She's already back.
Huh?
Hey!
If it is Yamada!
What?
Uh, can somebody explain why she's so intoxicated?
It's my fault for urging her to try a taste of the sake one of my friends gifted to us.
It's not you, Mr. Kamata!
Akane's so wasted because she was guzzling it like crazy!
And then she got all hyper and wouldn't stop bugging me, which was seriously annoying!
Akane's the type who gets really cheerful when she's had one too many, huh?
Yamada, I'm leaving the rest to you.
If she gets on your nerves, you can leave her on the restroom floor.
That's what Bruna did.
No, I couldn't do that.
Come on, Akito!
Sit down with us and have some dinner!
I'll send Akane home and a taxi later, so no need to worry!
That won't be necessary.
I'll have Akito take Akanechi home, so it's all fine!
Really?
Mm-hmm!
Well, you're right, those two have grown rather closely, Lee.
I guess it would be better to leave it to him.
Come on!
You're so late, Yamada!
Yeah, sorry.
YUMMY!
Hey, maybe we should just pick someone up off the street now.
I bet.
Let's go.
Are there even any cute girls around now?
Here's water.
What the?
Oh crap, was I really just sleeping right here?
Yes.
Wow, I can't believe it.
Me neither.
Wow, you got me water!
I was just thinking about how parched I am.
How did you know that I wanted some water?
Because you made a commotion about it in song form.
Ah!
Me oh my!
My throat's so dry!
Desert chillin' with the real fun guy!
I'm so sorry for causing you trouble all the time.
I'll make sure I don't forget this favor.
Whenever I'm drunk, I can barely remember anything afterwards.
Right.
Oh, I'll make a note.
If I leave a record on my phone, I'll be set.
It's okay to forget, so let's just go home.
It's getting late.
Oh, you're right.
Just look at the time.
Hey, Yamada, you can go on ahead.
Going home with me would be a hassle for you.
It's not safe, so I'm taking you.
There are tons of drunks around here.
Other than you, I mean.
Sorry, my heel got stuck in a groove.
Huh?
Uh-oh.
Won't come out.
Hey, um, sorry again for causing you so much trouble.
It's really weshed in there.
Good.
Got it.
Ready to go?
Uh-oh.
Yeah.
Well…
Okay, then. I'll be going now. Have a good night.
Thanks so much. Get home safely, okay?
Hey!
Uh, do you...
Uh, I mean, by any chance, do you like me, Yamada?
Uh, what? No. It's just... I, uh, I just had a feeling...
Because... his hand...
You got me.
When his hand was touching mine...
Huh? That means...
It seemed like he was telling me that.
I, uh... I'm pretty drunk right now.
Am I talking normally?
What I meant to say is that...
I like you.
I... like you, Akane.
And if you don't remember when you wake up in the morning, it's okay.
I'll say it again.
Until you remember.
Have a good night now.
Tomorrow, in the morning, when I wake up...
Is it okay if I call you?
Because I know I'm going to worry...
That all of this...
Was a dream.
That's okay with you.
Right?
I'll call you.
Tomorrow.
In the morning, when you wake up.
.
Hey...
Good morning.
Good morning!
So?
And then what happened?
How'd the phone call go? I want to know every word you guys said verbatim!
Oh, come on. That's private info.
What? You have a boyfriend now, Akane?
Way to go, girl!
Could it be that I'm the only one of us who doesn't have a boyfriend?
Wow, so he's a younger guy!
Yep.
I couldn't date somebody who's younger than me again.
Really? Why not?
It sort of felt like he was looking for a mature woman.
So I wasn't able to let myself depend on him.
He told me he could never get what I was thinking.
So dating a younger guy ended up being pretty hard for me.
But I get the sense that you'll be just fine, Akane.
You say that because it doesn't concern you.
Well, it really doesn't.
Get a grip, Akane.
Would you mind not acting depressed in front of single women like me?
Apologies.
Hmm. Well, it's okay.
I always knew that the two of you would end up together sooner or later.
Did you really?
Yeah, you guys gave off that kind of scent.
Scent?
Wait, I didn't really seem like I was throwing myself at Yamada, did I?
No, no.
Mm-hmm.
The other way around.
So anyway, in other words, what I'm trying to say is, you'll be taking your entrance exams soon, won't you?
I know that you're gonna be totally swamped, so you don't have to worry about me, okay?
I'll do everything in my power to try and not be a burden on you.
But still, every once in a while, like when you're tired, I'll be there for you to lean on me, all right?
Okay? At least pretend to listen.
No, I was listening. At least until you said that thing about people supporting each other.
That was way back at the beginning.
Yeah, to be honest, it was around that point I started to lose you.
The thing is, Akane, while I was looking at your mouth open and close, I happened to notice that your canine teeth are pointy.
Kay!
And while gazing at them, I was thinking they were really cute.
You!
Hmm?
You're teasing me, aren't you?
No, not at all.
This mature woman thing ain't working.
I'll walk you home.
Thanks.
By the way...
Yes?
What was it that you wanted to say earlier?
Well, um...
Actually...
I was trying to tell you I wanted to hold hands when we're walking.
Oh.
I'm sorry.
Wasn't that a cryptic way of telling me, though?
I'll try working on that.
That would be great.
What is this?
A shoe?
It must be a shoe, I guess.
Does this even function as a shoe?
Nah.
It turned out like that because it malfunctioned.
If you're going to crumple up on the ground,
shouldn't you wear normal shoes that are functional?
I just don't get them.
Women...
Are you okay?
Thank you.